{
    "subject": "resource/Horace_Lyne",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Newport,_Wales",
    "human_readable": "Horace Lyne was born in Newport, Wales.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8415572047233582,
            "question": "Where was Horace Lyne born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7959779500961304,
            "question": "Were there any famous people born in Newport, Wales?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4680790901184082,
            "question": "Are there any notable landmarks in Newport, Wales?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4109288454055786,
            "question": "What is the history of Newport, Wales?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39606067538261414,
            "question": "What country is Newport in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38361284136772156,
            "question": "What is the culture like in Newport, Wales?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3546726405620575,
            "question": "What might Horace Lyne be known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30056050419807434,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Horace Lyne's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25938987731933594,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Horace Lyne?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2515125274658203,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Newport, Wales?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Horace Lyne was born in Newport, Wales.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8214_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Horace Lyne?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8214_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Horace Lyne's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8214_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might Horace Lyne be known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8214_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8214_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8214_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8214_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8214_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8214_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8214_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8214_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8214_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8214_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8214_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the information provided in the document with the file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8214/re-ranker-msmarco/57.txt` and `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8214/re-ranker-msmarco/66.txt`, which mentions that Horace Lyne was a rugby player born in Newport, Wales."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}